http://www.iugg.org/privacy.php

IUGG Privacy Policy
Last Updated: 24 October 2018
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to the International Union of Geodesy and Geophysics (IUGG). This Privacy Policy explains what data we may collect from you and how we may use, store, and transfer your information. We may make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we do, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the IUGG website so that you will always know what information we collect and how it might be used. This Privacy Policy was last modified on 24 October 2018.
Who we are
International Union of Geodesy and Geophyiscs (IUGG) - Secretariat
c/o German Research Centre for Geosciences (GFZ)
Telegrafenberg A17
14473 Potsdam
Germany
T: +49 331 288 1978
F: +49 331 288 1759
secretariat@iugg.org
What personal information the IUGG collects about you
When you interact with the IUGG e.g., by taking a role within IUGG or within one of its sub-entities (incl., Associations, National Committees etc.), or by signing up to receive e-mails through the mailing list, IUGG receives and collects personal information about you. This personal information may include first name, surname, title, role within IUGG, physical (work) address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address.
How the IUGG uses personal information
The IUGG uses the information we receive from our sub-entities and collect about you to stay in contact with the IUGG community; to be able to inform you about important announcements, events, and other relevant news; to provide you with information that you have requested; or to communicate relevant information about IUGG projects, data, services, and other updates. Depending on your role within IUGG or within one of its sub-entities, this personal information might be published on the IUGG website or in the IUGG Yearbooks subject to your consent. We keep your information for no longer than is necessary for the purposes it was collected for.
Updating or deleting your personal information
The accuracy of your personal information is important to the IUGG. You can modify or delete your personal information incl. updating your subscription to the IUGG E-Journal by contacting the IUGG Secretariat (secretariat@iugg.org). Requests to unsubscribe may not take effect immediately.
Protecting personal information
The IUGG uses safeguards to ensure that your personal information is secure. Once we have received your information, we will use appropriate procedures and security features intended to prevent unauthorized access to our database.
Requesting removal of content from IUGG online resources
You have a right to your privacy. We would like to assure that we address your privacy concerns. If you identify any content you desire to be removed, please contact the IUGG Secretariat (secretariat@iugg.org). You can file a complaint about how we process your personal information by contacting the IUGG Secretariat (secretariat@iugg.org).
IUGG HOME
ABOUT IUGG
ASSOCIATIONS
UNION COMMISSIONS
SCIENTIFIC MEETINGS
EDUCATION & CAPACITYBUILDING
YOUNG SCIENTISTS
MEMBERS
Calendar | Members | Join | Assemblies | Publications | Links | Privacy Policy
